KATELYN MICHALOVE

Product Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com

615-613-5617

katelynmichalove.com

SUMMARY

I am a Product Designer with skills in conducting user research, leading projects, wireframing, visual design, and using and contributing to design systems. I've collaborated with executives, outside design vendors, end users, and internal teams to reach multiple product goals. My goal is to solve for user needs while balancing and meeting business objectives.

SKILL SET

UX/UI Design
Visual Design
User Research
Market Research
Usability Testing
Information Architecture
Branding

Prototyping

Frontend Development

TOOLS

Jira

Adobe Creative Suite
Optimal Workshop
Usability Hub
Lookback, Loom
Omnigraffle, Axure
Sketch, Figma
InVision, Marvel
Git & GitHub
HTML, CSS

EXPERIENCE

Sunbelt Rentals / Product Designer

July 2019 - present Remote

- Command Center Equipment Management Software
 Design lead for the complete redesign of Command Center.
 Conducted stakeholder interviews, user interviews, launched a customer survey, and took designs from wireframes to launch on an agile team.
- VDOS- Vehicle Dispatch Software

Product redesign involving field interviews and observations, wireframing new solutions and features to solve dispatcher needs, using the design system while adding new necessary visual components, usability testing and iteration.

SmartEquip - iOS Mobile Inspection Application
 1 Week sprint redesign to improve the user flows, match iOS
 HIG, convert visual design to Sunbelt branding guidelines, and create new necessary visual components. Later, an additional use case to solve for a UX problem encountered in pilot.

Freelance / Product Designer

August 2018- July 2019 Remote

- UX Design- Competitive Analysis, User Stories, User Flows, Wireframing, Prototyping, User Testing
- Visual Design- Branding, High Fidelity Mockups, Prototyping, User Testing, Webflow

Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer

June 2017 - July 2018 Sacramento, CA

 Led troubleshooting group through the stages of problem solving from exploration to documentation.

EDUCATION

University of Tennessee / 2017 / BA Chemical Engineering

Bloc / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship Remote program focused on designing 5 projects with consistent feedback through mentorship, grading team, and daily design critiques.